{
    "subject": "resource/Howard_Dietz",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Howard Dietz",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Howard Dietz is Howard Dietz.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9855125546455383,
            "question": "Is 'Howard Dietz' the full name of this person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9852212071418762,
            "question": "What is the full name of Howard Dietz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9622510075569153,
            "question": "Who is Howard Dietz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9437428116798401,
            "question": "What is the last name of Howard Dietz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9149240255355835,
            "question": "Does Howard Dietz have any other known names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9059308171272278,
            "question": "What is the first name of Howard Dietz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7617398500442505,
            "question": "What information do we know about Howard Dietz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7022740244865417,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Howard Dietz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6729797720909119,
            "question": "Is there anything else we should know about Howard Dietz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5475121736526489,
            "question": "How can we learn more about Howard Dietz?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Howard Dietz is Howard Dietz.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8892_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else we should know about Howard Dietz?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8892_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Howard Dietz?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8892_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What information do we know about Howard Dietz?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8892_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8892_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8892_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8892_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8892_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8892_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8892_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8892_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8892_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8892_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8892_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide biographical information about Howard Dietz, confirming that his full name is indeed Howard Dietz."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}